class Main {

  public static void main(String[] args) {
    
    int first = 10;
    int second = 20;

    // add two numbers
    int sum = first + second;
    System.out.println(first + " + " + second + " = "  + sum);
  }
}

Enter two numbers
10 20
The sum is: 30

In this program, two integers 10 and 20 are stored in integer variables first and second respectively.

Then, first and second are added using the + operator, and its result is stored in another variable sum.

Finally, sum is printed on the screen using println() function.